The world, what a glorious place.
Seek freedom and it will lie stretched out
before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides your restless
spirit, seize it, raise your flag and
stand tall.
Think back to the time when my search first
began Left behind those shores of sand
For the endless everlasting world out
there I know that with this burning passion
driving me Someday somewhere I'll finally
see The light I have searched for
everywhere.
When the summer sun is shining, shaking
the sails of my heart, I know I'll be able
to see.
A brand new world that had been hiding Has
opened up its doors for me to go Away
from the sky Weigh it in a tub of waves
The more despair I can be saved For the
horizon on the other side is Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah Is what I am for And though I
travel far from where my search began
Overseas of green and shores of sand Through
the endless everlasting.
I know that with this burning passion
driving me somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere.
Come on, you guys, wake up!
Wake up!
Nami, morning.
How about a passionate good morning kiss?
You bastard, your disgusting face nearly
scared me half to death!
I scared you?
What the hell do you think you're. ..
There's an island up ahead!
Guys, did you hear me?
Island?
An island?
Where?
Over there.
This island looks like it should be full
of big, strong, crazy monsters!
Ow!
My nose still isn't working right!
Look what you did!
It could be permanently broken!
Nothing here feels out of the ordinary.
It appears to be a small island.
Look, Nami!
Fruits like this are perfect for
replenishing our food supply.
And judging from this crop, there's no
shortage of goodies!
Wow.
We should find as many as we can and load
them on the ship.
I bet there are plenty of plants and
vegetables we can use for food, too.
With all it has to offer, this little
island seems like a cook's paradise.
Okay, then.
It'll be your job to look for anything we
can use as a source of food.
As for the rest of you, here.
What's that?
Draw lots?
It's simple.
The three who draw the shortest lots will
spend all day collecting this fruit.
And whoever draws the longest lot will have
the duty of staying here to protect the
ship.
And just who made you captain?
Why do you get to give all the orders?
Back off.
I may not be the captain, but who else is
going to do it?
Look, all of them are kind of short.
Why don't you draw three?
You're only supposed to take one.
I thought the person who grabs the most is
the winner.
I don't think further explanation on this
subject is necessary.
Do you?
Not at all.
I know.
Am I great or what?
You idiot!
I drew the long one, so. ..
I stay and watch the ship?
That's right!
Just make sure to keep her in one piece,
okay?
Hurry up, hurry up, let's go!
There's lots of fruit waiting to be
picked!
You're coming with us, Nami, right?
No thanks.
While you guys are gathering supplies, I'm
going to spend the day measuring the
island, so I'll be able to add it to our
sea charts.
Now let's get to work!
Be careful!
See you guys later!
Have a good one!
You too!
Look after the ship!
The one who collects the most fruit is the
winner!
Going to be a long day.
All right, it's time.
Measuring, measuring.
Oh, how lively Nami is when she's taking
measurements.
The tools on her back glistening in the
sunlight.
Stop acting stupid and catch up already.
I'm all alone today.
The ship looks really big, especially when
no one's around.
Listen up, guys.
Today I am in charge of the Going Merry.
That's Captain Chopper to you.
And remember, I'm the law.
Lopi, don't eat food that doesn't belong
to you.
Usopp, you need to work harder and no
excuses.
Sanji, prepare special dishes to satisfy
my every craving.
Hail me!
Hurrah!
How long have you been sitting there, huh?
Being so quiet, very sneaky.
You, you spy!
I still don't trust you.
I see what you're doing and I'm not fooled
for a second.
You were a Baroque Works officer agent.
You've been nothing but a selfish rogue
all your life, mean and stupid.
I won't accept you as a crewman, not even
if Luffy himself vouched for you.
Monster!
Her special skill is assassination, right?
I hear she's also very smart.
Need to be careful.
That's right, I almost forgot.
Before I went to bed last night, I made
ten rumble balls.
I'll spend the rest of the day making
more, quietly, safe and sound.
Good old rumble balls.
I have to make them whenever I can, since
there's no telling when we might run into
enemies.
Still, this takes me back to when I made
my first rumble ball.
Don't think Dr. Eam will notice that these
get reduced little by little.
She always mixes a little bit of this and
this, right?
Or was it this one?
She didn't put this one in, did she?
Chopper?
Do you know where my medicine bottles are?
They have important ingredients in them.
They're very rare and valuable medicines.
I'd better not find that you've been
playing with them.
Do you hear me?
Chopper?
Then I received a good scolding from
Doctorine that I'll never forget.
I wonder how Doctorine is getting along
these days.
I think I'll write her a letter.
So, they're called Rumble Balls, right?
You're trying to uncover the secret of the
Rumble Ball, aren't you?
And once you get it, you're going to
assassinate me!
But that's not going to happen.
I won't be taken down by a snake like you!
Rumble!
Guard point!
And now, heavy point!
Jumping point!
Burn point!
See the power of the rumble ball!
You are no match for the rumble ball.
It can give me the ability to find your
weak point.
Brain point, wide scope!
Point?
Where's her weak point?
Hey, what do you find so funny?
Look, there's no need to be afraid.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Hey, stop it!
Stop it!
Stop tickling me!
Aren't you just the cutest furball?
I do like you.
Cutest?
Give me a break!
I'm not falling for your flattery!
Think by making me happy it'll throw me
off guard or something?
Come on!
Do I look happy to you?
Can't fool me!
I gotcha!
I'm in!
I'm wise to your day!
Well then, shall we go?
Don't we need to refill the water you just
wasted?
I like to drink a cup of coffee.
On deck while reading.
What's the matter?
It's only fair that you go draw the water
since you're the one who spilt it in the
first place.
Yes!
Geez, how could I even contemplate working
on such a beautiful day like this?
Whoa, lots of monkeys.
Ooh!
He got me.
My life flashed before my eyes.
I thought that was it.
The end of Captain Osop.
No more adventures.
I didn't get a good look at what attacked
me, but it must have been a huge condor.
Why me?
Because I had to fight for my life, I
couldn't gather a single piece of fruit.
Oh, well.
That's okay.
No need for anyone to worry about me.
Again.
I wish somebody would give me a good
explanation why I have to take orders from that
woman.
Seriously, she's going to drive me insane.
Three sword style. .. Dragon. .. Twister!
Where's the contour line?
That's it!
The right ridgeline is right around 42
degrees.
What a coincidence!
If you measured my love for you, it would
be exactly 42 degrees Celsius!
Move it, moron!
I'm the one who's gotta fetch the water.
Why is she tagging along?
What a nice day.
What? !
You scared me to death!
What's wrong? !
Nothing.
Just commenting.
On a beautiful day.
I've been longing to take a walk like
this.
I haven't felt such peace for quite some
time.
In the past, it seemed like I was always
wound too tight from repressing my
emotions.
I never got the chance to smile.
So, um, if I remember the story correctly,
didn't you say you've been alone since
you were eight or so?
That's right.
I spent most of my youth following
pirates, and I barely survived.
It's your turn.
Tell me about this Dr. Rean person.
You were talking about her earlier.
She's a doctor, right?
She's your teacher.
A mentor, perhaps?
Uh, yeah, kind of.
Dr. Rean is someone I owe a great debt to.
Most people refer to her as Dr. Kureha.
Dr. Pereja, what is she like?
She really loves alcohol, but the best way
to describe her is a woman who's like a
pirate who's also a doctor.
Did I mention she really loves alcohol?
I studied under Dr. Ian for about six
years.
I wanted to be a doctor myself, you know.
That was my passion.
After mixing these three types of herbs
together in a large bowl, grind them well.
Chopper!
Are you finished with your reading?
I expect all 500 pages memorized.
You were playing around with my medicines
again.
No, I was experimenting.
That's the same as playing.
No excuses.
But I've been studying for three years
now, Dr. Correja.
I've read and re-read over 200 medical
books and journals.
Please let me help prepare the medicine.
You're about a hundred years from that.
I've memorized every single word that I've
ever read.
It's true.
I swear it.
I even managed to memorize the seventh
principle by Dr. Alexandra, cover to cover.
That's the one you said was the most
difficult book you ever read.
So, what does.
You okay?
It seems I've been infected with the
febrile disease from the patient I saw the
other day.
You're burning up!
Chopper, anyone can memorize words, but
now you must put what you've learned to the
test.
I guess this will make me your very first
patient.
I won't give you a single word of advice.
You're on your own.
If you fail, I'll die.
No pressure.
Learn the ultimate lesson.
Once you decide to practice medicine, you
take the responsibility of your
patients'lives in your hooves.
Can a blue-nosed reindeer master such a
burden?
There's no mistake.
This is the pathogen of the mandolin
virus.
What would work best to counteract it?
Found it!
Dr. Rean.
Don't die.
Please.
Let's see.
Dr. Kureha, aren't you going to ask what
sort of ingredients I combine?
Most patients will have little knowledge
of medicine or what is used to compound it.
They simply trust their doctor's judgment
and abide by whatever prescription he
gives them.
Alright, do you feel a little better?
Dummy, no medicine works instantaneously.
Go, I need to sleep for a while.
Chopper!
Not a bad job, considering your lack of
experience.
That was the first time that Dr. Ian truly
praised my aptitude in medicine.
And it was the only time throughout the
six years I worked under her.
Instead of giving me verbal acknowledgements,
she proved her faith in me by placing
her life in my hands.
That's Dr. Ian for you.
She believes in actions, not words.
And I agree with her.
Someday I'll become a great doctor, one
that'll surprise even her!
Oh no!
I think I said too much!
Hey!
The sun will be setting soon.
We should go.
I wish I had someone in my life who I had
a strong connection with.
Just like you do.
This is really. .. Heavy. ..
Go on.
Explain to me why you weren't able to
gather so much as a single piece of fruit.
That's a good question.
What's your answer?
I thought I was being attacked.
By a huge condor who was trying to claw my
face off!
Sorry, I failed you.
I tried my best, I really did, but I guess
in the end it wasn't good enough.
And now I'm dead.
I have to hand it to you, Zoro.
You did an impressive job today.
So impressive that you should just keep
working the rest of the night.
How lovable Nami is, even when she's
yelling at everyone.
Oh, shut up!
You're a moron!
You want some of me, moss head?
You two calm down.
Oh, I can't remember the last time we had
a nice, peaceful day like this.
Hey, Chopper, was it tough being alone all
day on the ship?
Kind of.
It was a chore.
But way more fun than I've had in a long
time.